<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<BookDescRoot xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <bookDescList>
    <BookDesc BookID="10000001">
      <BookName />
      <TextList>
        <Desc>If you’re reading this, you probably want to know what happened to bring me to this point. Want to know what happened to my reality? It’s distorted. Everything. From The Head’s home in A-Corp to the Outskirts. Everything has been corrupted, the Light twisted and rotten thanks to the Ensemble. I wasn’t strong enough to stop it. None of us were.

I’ll admit, once that fact really sunk in, I snapped. When I first came to this reality, I did the first thing I could think of and started hunting down Distortions. Anyone who could have been a possible extra addition to the Reverberation Ensemble, I killed. Urban Plagues, Nightmares, Stars of the City, it didn’t matter to me how tough they were and how badly I was injured. I could only see the ocean of blood I had helped create drowning me, knowing that my choice to take revenge on Ayin led to my own downfall. Revenge isn’t everything, even if it can be a powerful motivator. Eventually it will lead to your mistakes strangling you. I’m just more aware of it than others.

They gave me a Color for it, if you hadn’t guessed. The Teal Archivist, they call me. A macabre catalog of Distortions killed by my hands. At times I still feel more like a Pale Ghost, drifting through the City with only short-term goals in front of me. I’ve been fighting against the inevitable for a while now.

Though I suppose my own share of tragedy isn’t much to talk about. Extraordinary due to my origins, but you already know enough about that to want something new, don’t you?

I admit, I got lucky when I took down Argalia. Roland had done most of the work, I just managed disarming and killing him with his own scythe. Why do you think I have it now? Granted if I had known what would happen, I likely wouldn’t have finished him off. When I took a portion of the Light for myself to remain human and keep it from the Ensemble, I took the Purple Tear’s book with me. What I wasn’t aware of until later was that I had grabbed a portion of the Light that contained something. Call it what you want. Data. Souls. Memories. Whatever.

Gebura and Roland were part of that Light, though I believe I only managed to grab part of Roland’s soul, for lack of a better word. Argalia, however, must have planned on it. It’s the only explanation I have for how I ended up with a fragment of him after he faded into the Light itself.

A key, he called it. A way to access my mind and take what he wanted. Something not even the fragment, Uberto now, knew about. They were both the gateway to my mind, and a way for Argalia to rid himself of thoughts and emotions he didn’t want. Like taking the sum of one’s conscience and throwing it away. I guess Uberto’s their own person now, having been attached to me long after Pluto returned their ‘half’ of Argalia’s soul. None of us realized it was just my own memories and knowledge he was handing over, instead of the one tiny scrap of decency the Blue Sicko had left.

Pluto felt so betrayed when we learned about what had happened. I guess that was the last straw for him continuing to stand by Argalia’s side, but I don’t know for sure. He’s a rather private man, even if I’d consider him a decent one, Distortion or not.

As for Iori? She was the first voice I became aware of. It took almost no time at all for her, though that was probably due to her ability and my own intentions with her book. She told me that her powers were interrupted by my actions, that she was unintentionally split off, like a fragment cut off from the source. An echo of consciousness, so to speak.. Even fleeing the Library, I had to cut a deal with her to reunite the Purple Tear with herself.

Yes, I admit it. I knew I would lose. The Library doesn’t allow Guests to win unless the Director allows it. Unless of course Carmen made an exception, her ‘will’ being what allowed prior Guests like Philip and Streetlight Office to flee the Library safely. I doubt I would be so lucky to receive her ‘generosity’ here. I wouldn’t accept it anyway. She screwed me over once, and she did the same to Pluto in the name of ‘helping’ me. I can’t trust her any more. I shouldn’t have to begin with, if I’m being honest.

Making a deal with Iori wasn’t a good idea either, but I was too afraid of dying and everything being in vain to just give up. I wanted some legacy and testament to the Patrons to continue on, rather than the twisted version of The City to be what we were known for.

So why take the risk now? After all, there’s no guarantee I’ll be released from the Library. I have shreds of power from four of the more notable Colors in the City from the last decade or so, all of whom I’m close to in one way or another. A few friends I made and let in on my little secret asked me that, once. They said I could lead an Office better than they could. That I could go wherever I wanted, or even lead an Association’s branch if I felt so inclined. I wish I could tell you, but truthfully, I don’t know myself.

I just hope that this timeline gives a version of myself the happy ending I wanted. I want so badly to have a part in it, but there’s no place for me in this reality…
</Desc>
      </TextList>
    </BookDesc>
  </bookDescList>
</BookDescRoot>